Harlan Fiske Stone Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1889-1946 (Box 4-30)
  - Tack, Augustus Vincent
  - Thacher, Thomas D.
  - Tinker, Edward Larocque
  - Towsley, Frank h.
  - Tsuchiya, Scotty H.
  - Turner, Charles H.
  - Turner, Lewis Clyde
    - 1924-1927
    - 1928-1930
    - 1931-1934
    - 1935-1938 (Box 29)
    - 1939-1942
    - 1943-1944
    - 1945-1946, undated
  - Turner, William P.
  - Tweed, Harrison See also Container 49, National Association of Legal Aid Organizations
  - Tyson, Levering
  - “U” miscellaneous
  - “V” miscellaneous
    - Va
    - Ve-Vr
  - Van Devanter, Willis See also Container 77, Van Devanter
  - Veverka, Ferdinand
  - Victor, Royall
  - “W” miscellaneous
    - Wa
    - We
    - Wh
    - Wi
    - Wo
    - Wr-Wy
  - Wadsted, Otto
  - Wankowicz, Witold
  - Warren, Charles (Box 30)
  - Warren, Charles Beecher
  - Wechsler, Herbert
  - Wehle, Louis B.
  - Welles, Sumner See Container 51, State Department
  - Wells, Ira K.
  - Westwood, Howard C.
  - Wheeler, George W. See Container 39, American Law Institute
  - Whitcomb, Harry E.
  - White, William Allen
  - Whitman, Malcolm D.
  - Wickersham, George W. See also Container 39, American Law Institute
  - Wiehr, P.
  - Wigmore, John H.
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman
  - Willebrandt, Mabel Walker
  - Wolkiser, Manfred
  - Woolsey, John
  - Wormser, I. Maurice
  - Wyzanski, Charles E., Jr.
  - “Y” miscellaneous
  - Yntema, Hessel E.
  - Young, Helen May
  - “Z” miscellaneous
  - Unidentified
- Special Correspondence, 1924-1946 (Box 31-38)
  Congratulatory messages received on his appointment as Attorney General, Associate Justice of the Supreme Court, and Chief Justice of the United States, and condelences on Stones's death.
  Arranged chronologically by occasion and grouped alphabetically therein by name correspondent.
  - Congratulations on appointment as Attorney General, 1924 (Box 31)
    - A-L, (11 folders)
    - M-Z, (7 folders) (Box 32)
  - Congratulations received by Agnes H. Stone
    - 1924
    - 1925
  - Congratulations on appointment to Supreme Court, 1925 (Box 33)
    - A-M, (8 folders)
    - N-Z, (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Congratulations on appointment as chief justice, 1941
    - A-D, (4 folders)
    - E-O, (9 folders) (Box 35)
    - P-Z, (5 folders) (Box 36)
    - Lists
  - Letters of condolence
    - “A-B” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - “C-M” miscellaneous, (10 folders) (Box 37)
    - “N-Z” miscellaneous, (7 folders) (Box 38)
    - Unidentified
    - Resolutions and statements
    - Messages from foreign governments
    - Memorials
- Subject File, 1899-1946 (Box 39-51)
  Letters received, copies of letters sent, memoranda, drafts of writings, reports, and near-print and printed material pertianing to cases in which Stone was actively involed.
  Arranged chronologically by court term and alphabetically by case name within each term.
  - Alpha Delta Phi (Box 39)
  - American Bar Association See also Container 43, Association of the Bar of the City of New York
  - American Commission for the Protection and Salvage of Artistic and Historic Monuments in Europe
  - American Law Institute
    - 1924
    - 1925
    - 1926
    - 1927
    - 1928-1931, 1933-1934
    - 1938-1942
  - American Philosophical Society
  - American Red Cross
  - Amherst College, Amherst, Mass. (Box 40)
    - 1912-1929
    - 1931-1932
    - 1933
      - Jan.-May
      - Sept.-Dec.
    - 1934
      - Jan.-Mar.
      - Apr.-May
      - Aug.-Dec.
    - 1935
    - 1936 (Box 41)
    - 1937
    - 1938, (2 folders)
    - 1939, (2 folders)
    - 1940
    - 1941 (Box 42)
    - 1942
    - 1943
    - 1944
    - 1945, (2 folders)
    - 1946 (foreword to book by Alfred E. Stearns)
    - Agenda, minutes, reports
      - 1937
      - 1945
    - “Bootlegging”
    - Financial reports, 1935-1940 (Box 43)
    - Honorary degrees
    - Printed matter
    - Reports, 1938-1939
  - Association of the Bar of the City of New York See also Container 39, American Bar Association
  - Athenaeum (club), London, England
  - Atlantic Gulf Oil Corp.
  - Attorney general's confidential file
    - Arizona
    - Boston-U.S. attorney
      - Choate, Charles F.
      - Harris, Robert O.
      - Hyde, Benjamin D.
    - Northern California judgeship
    - Northern District-California-U.S. attorney (Box 44)
    - Southern District-New York-U.S. attorney
    - Southern District-Ohio-judgeship
  - Ault, Maude
  - Bowdoin College, Brunswick, Maine, 1944
  - Clubs
  - Colgate University, Hamilton, N.Y., 1940-1944
  - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
    - 1924-1927
    - 1928-1940
    - 1941-1945
  - Columbia University Law School, New York, N.Y.
    - 1899-1903
    - 1905-1907, 1909
    - 1910-1911
    - 1915
    - 1916-1917 (Box 45)
    - 1918-1920
    - 1921-1922
    - 1923
    - Congratulations on appointment as dean, 1910
  - Commission of Fine Arts
  - Commonwealth Fund Legal Research Committee
    - Correspondence, 1924-1926
    - Manuscript
  - Conscientious objectors, World War I, 1929-1945
  - Coolidge, Calvin-memorial service, 1933
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C.
  - District of Columbia police situation, 1940
  - Dumbarton Oaks, Washington, D.C, 1942-1946
  - Education, 1923-1942
  - First Congregational Church, Washington, D.C., 1925-1930
  - Folger Shakespeare Library, Washington, D.C.
    - Adams, Joseph Quincy
      - 1935-1936
      - 1937
      - 1938
      - 1939-1943 (Box 46)
      - Undated
    - Annual reports
      - 1933-1936
      - 1936-1940
    - Book purchases
    - Folger, Mrs. Henry C.
      - 1932-1933
      - 1933-1935
    - Law exhibit
    - Miscellaneous
    - Printed matter
    - Reports
    - Slade, William A. (Box 47)
      - 1931-1932
      - 1933
      - 1934
    - Theatre, 1935-1938
    - Wills and agreements
  - Gunston Hall, Mason Neck,. Va.
  - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell
  - Honorary degrees
  - Hoover, Herbert, (3 folders)
  - Huntington Library and Art Gallery, San Marino, Calif. (Box 48)
  - Isle au Haut dredging project
  - Kenyon College, Gambier, Ohio
  - Law clerks
  - Law clerks recollections
  - Legal Aid Society
  - Library of Congress
  - Lincoln, Abraham (printed matter)
  - Lincoln's Inn, London, England
  - Literary Society
  - Lockwood Manufacturing Co.
  - “Medicine ball cabinet” parties
  - Memberships (honorary and others)
  - Michigan (University of) Law School, Ann Arbor, Mich.
  - Morris Plan Insurance Society (Box 49)
  - Morrow, Dwight W.
  - National Association of Legal Aid Organizations
  - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement, 1929
    - Correspondence
    - Printed matter
  - National Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C.
    - Cairns, Huntington, secretary
    - Dale Collection
    - Endowment Fund-Trust Indenture
    - Finley, David E., director
    - Kress Collection
    - Minutes and agendas
      - 1941-1942
      - 1943
      - 1944
    - Miscellaneous (Box 50)
    - Printed matter
    - Reports
    - Salaries and appointments
    - Widener Collection
  - Newburyport, Mass.
  - Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio
  - Ormsby, George F.
  - Ownbey, James A.
  - Princeton University, Princeton, N.J.
  - Recommendations, requests for
  - Rubber, 1942 (Box 51)
  - Sapp, M. Louise
  - Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C.
    - Financial
    - Freer Gallery
    - Minutes of meetings
    - Miscellaneous
  - State Department
  - Syracuse University, Syracuse, N.Y.
  - Travel data and passport
  - Tufts College, Medford, Mass.
  - United States v. Rodiek, Executor of John F. Hackfield
  - Washington Monument Society
  - Yeshiva College, New York, N.Y.
- Supreme Court File: Case File, 1924-1946 (Box 52-73)
  Notes, opinions, correspondence, and other material pertaining to cases in which Stone was actively involved. Names of cases have been copied directly from the folder labels set up by Justice Stone's office. Case files indicated as "empty" were received in that state and have been maintained in the Case File series to provide a complete listing of the files. See explanation of folder labels in Container 52.
  - Explanation of folder labels (Box 52)
  - 1924 Term
    - Cement Manufacturers Protective Ass'n. et. Al. V. United States
    - Dumbra v. United States
    - Edward Hines Yellow Pine Trustees v. Martin
    - Knewel v. Egan
    - Maple Flooring Ass'n. v. United States
    - May v. Henderson
    - North Laramie Land Co. V. Hoffman
    - Second Russian Insurance Co. v. Miller
    - Stebbins v. Riley
    - Stowell v. Federal Reserve Bank
    - United States v. Dunn
  - 1925 Term
    - Anderson v. United States
    - Arkansas v. St. Louis-San Francisco Ry.
    - Barnett v. Wells Fargo Nat. Bank
    - Beazell v. Ohio
    - Blair, Comm'r. V. Birkenstock
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Ry. Co. v. Thompson Mfg. Co.
    - City of Douglas v. Federal Reserve Bank
    - Concrete Appliances Co. V. Gomery
    - General American Tank Car Corp. v. Day
    - Hartsville Oil Mill v. United States
    - Hurwitz v. North
    - Kansas City Steel Co. v. Arkansas
    - Louisville & Nashville R.R. v. Sloss-Sheffield Co.
    - Massachusetts v. New York et. al.
    - Metcalf & Eddy v. Mitchell, Adm'x.
    - Provost v. United States
    - Raffel v. United States
    - Reading Co. v. Koons (Box 53)
    - Risty v. Chicago, R. I. & Pacific Ry. Co.
    - Roberts and Schaefer Co.v. Emmerson
    - Schlesinger v. Wisconsin
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Ry. Co. v. Mills
    - Towar Mills v. United States
    - United States v. Katz
    - Weaver v. Palmer Bros. Co. (empty)
  - 1926 Term
    - Baltimore S.S. Co.v. Phillips (empty)
    - Bedford Co. v. Stone Cutters Ass'n. (empty)
    - Brasfield et al. v. United States
    - DiSanto v. Pennsylvania
    - Duignan v. United States
    - Fairmont Co. v. Minnesota
    - Federal Trade Commission v. Eastman Co.
    - Federal Trade Commission v. Western Meat Co. (empty)
    - Fidelity National Bank and Trust Co. v. Swope
    - First National Bank of Hartford v. City of Hartford
    - Fort Smith Light & Traction Co. v. Paving District No. 16
    - Fox River Co. v. Railroad Commission
    - Georgetown National Bank v. McFarland
    - Goodyear Tire & Rubber Co. v. United States
    - Great Northern Railway et al. v. Sutherland, Alien Property Custodian (empty)
    - Hayman v. City of Galveston
    - Hudson v. United States
    - Independent Coal & Coke Co. v. United States
    - Kercheval v. United States (empty)
    - Ley & Co. v. United States
    - McCardle et al. v. Indianapolis Water Co. (empty)
    - McGuire v. United States
    - Miller v. Milwaukee (empty)
    - Minnesota v. First National Bank
    - Missouri ex. rel. v. Public Serv. Comm'n
    - Myers v. United States, (7 folders) (Box 54)
    - New York Dock Co. v. Poznan
    - Nicholas v. Coolidge
    - Ohio ex rel. Clarke v. Deckebach
    - One Ford Coupe Automobile, United States v. (empty)
    - Pizitz Dry Goods Co. v. Yeldell
    - Portneuf-Marsh Valley Canal Co. v. Brown Trustees
    - Seeman et al. v. Philadelphia Warehouse Co.
    - Smith v. Wilson
    - Smyer v. United States
    - Southern Pacific Co. v. United States
    - Swiss Oil Corp. v. Shanks
    - Tyson Brother v. Banton
    - United States v. New York Central R. R. Co.
    - United States ex. Rel. Norwegian Co. v. Tariff Commission
    - United States v. Trenton Potteries Co.
    - United States v. White Dental Mfg. Co.
    - Vajtauer v. Comm'r. of Immigration
    - Van Oster v. Kansas (empty)
    - Waggoner Estate v. Wichita County et al.
  - 1927 Term
    - Black & White Taxi v. Black & Yellow Taxi
    - Blair, Comm'r v. Oesterlein Machine Co.
    - Blodgett v. Holden (empty)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul & Pacific R.R. Co. v. Risty et al.
    - Equitable Trust Co. of New York v. First National Bank of Trinidad
    - Equitable Trust Co. v. Rochling et al.
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co. v. United States
    - Heiner, Collector v. Colonial Trust Co. (empty)
    - Heiner, Collector v. Tindle
    - Holland Furniture Co. v. Perkins Glue Factory
    - Ingram-Day Lumber Co. v. McLouth
    - Interstate Busses Corp. v. Blodgett
    - Jenkins, Receiver v. National Surety Co. (Box 55)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Co. v. Ellzey
    - Lamborn v. Nat'l. Bank of Commerce
    - Latzko v. Equitable Trust Co.
    - Lewellyn, Collector v. Electric Reduction Co.
    - Long v. Rockwood (empty)
    - Louisville Gas Co. v. Coleman
    - The Malcolm Baxter, Jr.
    - Miller v. Schoene
    - Nagle, Comm'r v. Loi Hoa-Lam Young
    - National Life Ins. Co. v. United States
    - Olmstead et al. v. United States
    - Panhandle Oil Co. v. Knox (empty)
    - People of Sioux Country Nebraska v. National Surety Co.
    - Quaker City Cab Co. v. Pennsylvania
    - Reinecke, Collector, v. Gardner, Trustee
    - Ribnik v. McBride
    - Saltonstall v. Saltonstall
    - Shaw v. Gibson-Zahniser Oil Corp.
    - Sisseton and Wahpeton Bands of Sioux Indians v. United States
    - Stipcich v. Metropolitan Life Ins. Co.
    - Tucker v. Alexander, Collector
    - Untermyer v. Anderson
    - Western Union Telegraph Co. v. Priester
    - Williamsport Wire Rope Co. v. United States
    - Willing v. Chicago Auditorium Association
    - Work, Secretary of Interior v. Braffet
    - Wuchter v. Pizzutti
  - 1928 Term
    - Boston Sand Co. v. United States
    - Central New England Railway Co. v. Boston & Albany Railroad Co.
    - Chase National Bank v. United States
    - Compania General de Tabacos de Philipinas v. Collector of Internal Revenue
    - Frost v. Corporation Commission
    - Gilchrist v. Interborough Rapid Transit Co.
    - Gleason v. Seaboard Air Line Ry. Co.
    - Gulf Refining Co. v. Atlantic Mutual Insurance Co.
    - Helson & Randolph v. Kentucky
    - International Shoe Co. v. Shartel, Attorney General of Missouri
    - Johnson v. Shipping Board
    - Jordan, Secretary of State, et al. V. Tashiro
    - Kirk et al. v. Maumee Valley Elec. Co.
    - Kirk et al. v. Providence Mill Co.
    - Leonard v. United States (Box 56)
    - Louisville & Nashville R.R. Co. v. Chatters
    - Lucas, Collector v. Alexander et al.
    - Macallen Co. v. Massachusetts
    - Morimura Co. v. Taback Brothers
    - New York v. Latrobe, Jr.
    - N.Y. Central R. R. Co. v. Johnson
    - Nielson, Administrator v. Johnson
    - Northern Coal Co. v. Strand
    - Reinecke, Collector v. Northern Trust Co.
    - St. Louis & O'Fallon R.R. v. United States
    - Standard Oil Co. v. City of Marysville
    - State of Washington v. Roberge
    - United Fuel Gas Co. v. Public Service Commission of West Virginia
    - United Fuel Gas Co. v. Railroad Commission of Kentucky
    - Williams v. Standard Oil Co. of La. (empty)
  - 1929 Term
    - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Ry. V. Toops
    - Baizley Iron Works v. Span
    - Baldwin v. Missouri
    - Broad River Power Co. v. South Carolina ex. rel. Daniel, Atty. Gen (empty)
    - Bromley v. McCaughn, Collector
    - Carley & Hamilton Inc. v. Snook
    - Carpenter v. Shaw, State Auditor
    - Charter Shipping Co. Ltd. v. Bowring, Jones & Tidy Ltd.
    - Clarke v. Haberlee Brewing Co.
    - Collie v. Ferguson et al.
    - District of Columbia v. Fred
    - Dohany v. Rogers, State Highway Comm'r.
    - Employers Liability Assurance Co. v. Cook
    - Farmers Loan Co. v. Minnesota (empty)
    - Ford & Son, Inc. v. Little Falls Co.
    - Illinois Central R.R. Co. v. Crail
    - International Shoe Co. v. Federal Trade Commission
    - Missouri v. Gehner
    - New York Central R.R. Co. V. Marcone
    - Niles Bement Pond Co. v. United States
    - Pattton v. United States (empty)
    - Railroad Commission v. Los Angeles Ry. Corp.
    - Renziehausen v. Lucas, Commissioner
    - Richbourg Motors Co. v. United States
    - Safe Deposit & Trust Co. v. Virginia
    - Silver v. Silver
    - Toombs v. Citizens Bank of Waynesboro (Box 57)
    - United Railways v. West
    - United States v. Adams
    - U.S. Shipping Board Merchant Fleet Corp. v. Harwood, Trustee
    - Wisconsin v. Illinois, Michigan
  - 1930 Term
    - Alford v. United States
    - Aluminum Casting Co. v. Routzahn
    - Broad River Co. v. South Carolina
    - Burnet, Comm'r. v. Sanford Brooks Co.
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis & Omaha Ry. Co. v. Holmberg
    - Coolidge Trustees v. Long, Comm'r.
    - DeForest Radio Co. v. General Electric Co.
    - Educational Films Corp. v. Ward
    - Gambrinus Brewery Co. v. Anderson (empty)
    - Gasoline Products Co. Inc. v. Champlin Refining Co.
    - Group No. 1 Oil Corp. v. Bass, Collector
    - Husty v. United States
    - Indian Motorcycle Co. v. United States
    - International Paper Co. v. United States
    - McCaugn v. Hershey Chocolate Co.
    - Maynard, Adm'r v. Elliott, Trustee
    - Merchants Warehouse Co. v. United States
    - Milliken v. United States
    - Nash-Breyer Motor Co. v. Burnet
    - New Jersey v. New York
    - Oxford Paper Co. v. The Nidarholm
    - Pacific Gas and Electric v. Securities and Exchange Commission
    - Pagel, Adm'r. v. MacLean, Adm'r.
    - Prussian v. United States
    - Saranac Automatic Machine Corp. v. Wirebounds Patents Co.
    - Standard Marine Insur. Co. v. Scottish Metropolitan Assurance Co.
    - Susquehanna Power Co. v. State Tax Comm'n.
    - United States v. Bland
    - United States v. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul & Pacific R. Co.
    - United States v. Felt & Tarrant Mfg. Co.
    - United States v. MacIntosh
  - 1931 Term (Box 58)
    - Aetna Casualty & Surety Co. v. Phoenix National Bank & Trust Co.
    - American Hide & Leather Co. v. United States
    - Baltimore & Ohio R. Co. v. Berry
    - Blakely, Receiver v. Brinson
    - Boston and Maine Railroad v. Armburg
    - Bradford Electric Light Co. v. Clapper
    - Burnett v. Coronado Oil & Gas Co.
    - Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Ry. Co. v. United States
    - Colorado v. Symes, District Judge (empty)
    - Coombes v. Getz (empty)
    - Crowell v. Benson
    - First National Bank v. Maine
    - Handy v. Delaware Trust Co. (empty)
    - Hardware Dealers Mutual Fire Ins. Co. v. Glidden Co. et al.
    - Heiner v. Donnan
    - Lamb v. Cramer
    - Lamb v. Schmitt, Receiver
    - Lawerence v. State Tax Comm'n.
    - MacDonald, Trustee, etc. v. Plymouth County Trust Co.
    - MacLaughlin, Coll'r. v. Alliance Insurance Co.
    - Matson Navigation Co. v. United States
    - Matthews v. Rodgers et al.
    - Miller, Coll'r. v. Standard Nut Margarine Co.
    - New State Ice Co. v. Liebmann (empty)
    - Pacific Co., Ltd. v. Johnson, State Treas.
    - Page v. Arkansas Gas Corp.
    - Phillips, Coll'r. V. Dime Trust & Safe Deposit Co.
    - Reed v. Allen (empty)
    - Shearer v. Burnet, Comm'r
    - Shriver v. Woodbine Savings Bank
    - Stratton, Sec. of State v. St. Louis Southwestern Ry. Co.
    - United States v. Baltimore and Ohio RR.
    - United States v. Ryan
    - Utah v. United States
  - 1932 Term
    - Advance-Rumley Co. v. Jackson (empty)
    - Aetna Life Ins. Co. v. Moses
    - Anglo Chilean Corp. v. Alabama (empty)
    - Bankers Pocahontas Coal Co. v. Burnet, Comm'r
    - Burnet, Comm'r v. Aluminum Goods Mfg. Co.
    - Burnet, Comm'r v. Brooks (Box 59)
    - Burnet, Comm'r v. Harmel
    - Central Transfer Co. v. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis
    - Dickson v. Uhlmann Grain Co.
    - Edelman, StateTreasurer v. Boeing Air Transport, Inc.
    - Elting, Coll'r. v. North German Lloyd
    - Fairmount Glassworks v. Coal Co.
    - Gebardi v. United States
    - Grau v. United States (empty)
    - Hurn v. Oursler (empty)
    - I.C.C. v. Oregon, Washington RR. & Navigation Co. (empty)
    - Johnson & Higgins v. United States (empty)
    - Liggett Co. v. Lee
    - Lloyd Sabaudo Societa Anonima per Azioni v. Elting, Coll'r f Customs
    - Murphy Oil Co. v. Burnet, Comm'r
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Ry. Co. v. Wallace, Comptroller
    - Palmer v. Bender, Adm'x.
    - Pennsylvania R. Co. v. Chamberlain, Adm'x (empty)
    - Petroleum Exploration v. Burnett, Comm'r
    - Puerto Rico v. Russell & Co.
    - Reichelderfer v. Quinn
    - Rogers v. Guaranty Trust Co. (empty)
    - Sgro v United States
    - Strother v. Burnet, Comm'r
    - Texas & Pacific Ry. Co. v. United States, (2 folders)
    - United States v. Acme Operating Co.
    - United States v. Dakota-Montana Oil Co.
    - United States v. Dubilier Condenser Corp.
    - United States v. Flores
    - United States v. Shreveport Grain & Elevator Co.
    - United States ex rel. Greathouse et al. v. Dern, Secretary of War
    - Vermont v. New Hampshire
    - Washington Fidelity Insurance Co. v. Burton
    - Wood, Sec. of State v. Broom (empty)
  - 1933 Term
    - Alabama v. Arizona (empty)
    - Alaska Steamship Co. v. United States
    - Arrow-Hart & Hegeman Elec. Co. v. Federal Trade Commission
    - Aschenbrenner v. United States Fidelty & Guaranty Co.
    - Central Kentucky Natural Gas Co. v. Railroad Comm'n of Kentucky
    - Concordia Fire Insur. Co. v. Illinois
    - Connell v. Walker
    - Dakin, Receiver v. Bayly, Liquidator (Box 60)
    - Electric Cable Joint Co. v. Brooklyn Edison Co., Inc.
    - Factor v. Laubenehimer, U.S. Marshal, (2 folders)
    - Federal Compress Co. v. McLean
    - Federal Land Bank of Columbia, S.C. v. Gaines
    - Federal Trade Commission v. Keppel & Bro. Inc.
    - Freuler, Adm'r v. Helvering, Comm'r (empty)
    - Gilvary v. Cuyahoga Valley Ry.
    - Globe Indemnity Co. v. United States
    - Healy, Chief of Police v. Ratta
    - Helvering, Comm'r v. Falk Ex'rs
    - Helvering, Comm'r v. Newport Co.
    - Home Building and Loan Association v. John H. Blaisdell
    - Illinois Commerce Commission et al. v. United States et al.
    - Krauss Bros. Lumber Co. v. Dimon Steamship Corp.
    - Landress v. Phoenix Mutual Ins. Co.
    - Life & Casualty Ins. Co. v. Barefield (empty)
    - Nickey v. Mississippi
    - Ohio v. Helvering, Comm'r
    - Oklahoma Gas & Elec. Co. v. Oklahoma Packing Co. et al.
    - Pacific Telephone & Telegraph Co. v. Seattle
    - Puget Sound Power & Light Co. v. Seattle
    - Reynolds v. United States (empty)
    - Sanders v. Armour Fertilizer Works (empty)
    - Seattle Gas Co. v. City of Seattle
    - United States v. Illinois Central R. Co.
    - United States v. Louisiana
    - United States v. Murdock (empty)
    - Whitcomb v. Helvering, Comm'r.
    - Wolfe v. United States
    - Woodson v. Deutsch Gold & Silver
    - Yarborough v. Yarborough
  - 1934 Term
    - Alaska-Packers Ass'n v. Industrial Accident Comm'n of California
    - Altoona Publix Theatres, Inc. v. American Tri-Ergon Corp.
    - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Ry. Co. et al v. United States
    - Atlantic Coastline RR v. Florida (empty)
    - Awotin v. Atlas Exchange National Bank
    - Borden's Farm Products Co. v. Baldwin (Box 61)
    - Central Vermont Transportation Co. v. Durning, Collector of Customs
    - Detroit International Bridge Co. v. Corporation Tax Appeal Board of Michigan (empty)
    - Dimick v. Schiedt
    - Doleman v. Levine
    - Federal Land Bank of St. Louis v. Priddy, Circuit Judge
    - Georgia Railway & Electric Co. v. City of Decatur
    - Gordon, Sec'y of Banking v. Omnisky
    - Gordon v. Washington
    - Gulf, Mobile & Northern Railroad Co. v. Helvering, Comm'r
    - Hamilton v. Regents of Univ. of Calif.
    - Hartley v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue
    - Helvering v. Morgans
    - Helvering v. Rankin (empty)
    - Helvering v. Taylor (empty)
    - Helvering v. Union Pacific Railroad Co.
    - Herndon v. Georgia (empty)
    - Kimen v. Atlas Exchange National Bank
    - McCrea v. United States
    - McNally v. Hill, Warden
    - Metropolitan Casualty Ins. Co. v. Brownell
    - Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Railway v. Walters
    - Old Mission Portland Cement Co. v. Helvering, Comm'r
    - Panhandle Eastern Pipline Co. v. Highway Comm'n
    - Paramount Pulix Corp. v. American Tri-Ergon Corp.